Did you know many adults sit down for more than nine hours a day – maybe you're one of them!
你知道吗，许多成年人每天坐着的时间超过九小时——也许你就是其中之一！
Whether it's working at a desk, sitting motionless in a car, bus or train or lounging on the sofa watching TV, we have a much more sedentary lifestyle than our parents and grandparents did.
无论是在办公桌前工作，在汽车、公交车或火车上一动不动地坐着，还是慵懒地躺在沙发上看电视，与我们的父母和祖父母那一代相比，我们的生活方式更倾向于于久坐不动。
The question that this raises is just what is it doing to our bodies?
这种生活方式所引发的问题是，这到底对我们的身体有什么影响？
The news isn't good.
消息不太好。
A study carried out in the 1950s compared bus drivers with the conductors, who walked around the bus selling tickets.
一项在20世纪50年代进行的研究比较了公交车司机和在车上走动卖票的售票员。
It showed that drivers, who spent many hours sat at the wheel, were twice as likely to have heart attacks than the more active conductors.
结果显示，长时间开车的司机，其心脏病发作的可能性是更活跃的售票员的两倍。
In fact, prolonged sitting has been associated with a number of different conditions, even in people who otherwise take regular exercise.
事实上，长时间坐着与许多不同的健康状况有关，即使在那些平时定期锻炼的人中也是如此。
If you sit down all day, you burn far fewer calories than someone with a more active job.
如果你整天坐着，你燃烧的卡路里比从事更活跃工作的人少得多。
There are suggestions that it slows your metabolism and makes it harder for your body to regulate blood sugar levels, increasing the risk of diabetes.
有迹象表明，它会减慢你的新陈代谢，使你的身体更难调节血糖水平，从而增加患糖尿病的风险。
One possible answer to this problem is for desk workers to use standing desks, to spend at least part of their day on their feet.
这个问题的一个可能的解决方案是让伏案工作者使用站立式办公桌，每天至少有一部分时间站着。
One small study showed that office workers who stood for three hours after lunch had a much smaller increase in blood sugar levels, while another suggested that by standing for three or four hours a day over the period of a year, people would burn as many calories as if they had run ten marathons.
一项小型研究表明，午饭后站立三小时的办公室职员血糖水平的升幅要小得多，而另一项研究表明，如果一年中每天站立三到四个小时，人们燃烧的卡路里相当于跑了十个马拉松。
Other experts question this figure and point out that standing all day can also have negative impacts, such as leg or back pain, recommending that if people do want to use standing desks, they should gradually increase the amount of time that they spend on their feet.
其他专家对这个数字提出质疑，并指出整天站立也会产生负面影响，例如腿痛或背痛，他们建议，如果人们确实想使用站立式办公桌，应该逐渐增加站立的时间。
Crucially, they also point out that there are many alternatives to sitting, and that their impact is unlikely to be the same: walking, for example, burns far more calories than standing.
至关重要的是，他们还指出，除了坐着还有很多其他选择，它们的效果不太可能相同：例如，走路比站立燃烧的卡路里多得多。